Tamara Sidorova Junior Software Engineer

Cell: 617-775-1797 Email: tomatoma891@gmail.com

Overview:

I'm Full Stack Developer. Currently I'm in a coding bootcamp in University of Denver. I have experience in HMTL,CSS,JavaScript,Jquery,Ajax and Node.js. I enjoy working with variety of software and learning new product. I'm always trying to find a creative approach to problem solving and adapt quickly to changing priorities.

Work Experience:

• September 2019 – Present

Zen Planner, Daxko – Customer Advocate, Denver

• June 2018 –September 2019

Centura Health Physician Group- Customer Service Representative, Denver

• April 2018 – December 2018

Mobile Solutions/Startup Company – Customer Help Desk Specialist, Denver, CO

Projects:

- YOUR CITY GUIDE -is an application that assists the user in finding local events and dining options. As soon as the user selects a city from the drop down, they are then able to filter the type of entertainment (music, sports or art) that they are seeking, as well as select an option for local restaurants built with HTML,CSS,Materialize,Javascript,jQuery,Ticketmaster API,OpenTable API
- Weather Dashboard API- A weather dashboard is application with search
 functionality to find current weather conditions and the future weather outlook for
 multiple cities. Application uses icons to represent weather conditions. Application
 stores previously searched for cities in localstorage and displays them to the user.
 Application loads last searched city forecast on page load.

Education:

University of Denver Coding Bootcamp -Full Stack Web Developer;

Kazan Federal University- Bachelor's degree in Sociology;

Portfolio:

https://tomatoma891.github.io/updated-portfolio-/